Guide to the Office of Institutional Research, Yale University, Records and Reports
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1969-2014; Accession 2017-A-014
  - "Expository Writing at Yale, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Distributional Requirements, 1978-2004 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Graduate School financial aid reports, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Scheduled classroom hours, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Scheduled classroom hours, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
  - FAS science education past reports, 1939-1971 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - FAS faculty and student statistics-Ackerman, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Student organizations affiliated with Yale schools, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Daycare study, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Faculty maternity, paternity and child care policies-includes data from comparable schools, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Faculty club survey, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Faculty salary reports, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 23-23a)
  - Compensation report, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Columbia survey
    - 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 25a)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Cornell survey, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Cornell university statistical indicators, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Thirty-year follow up study of male college students, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Memoranda from Alison Richard to Yale community, 1996-2000 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - SAT evaluation (Rainbow Project), Circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Report: "Effect of Marginal Tax rates on Contributions to Yale, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Alumni fund: reports and working papers, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Alumni giving research project, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Patterns of giving-Office of Development, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Alumni giving study, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Report on minority students in Graduate and Professional Schools, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Budget assessments, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Report on the Women's Study Program, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Mellon Foundation "College and Beyond" Study
    - Data collection, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
    - Transcripts, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 12-16)
    - Freshman applications
      - Abbott-Austin, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Back-Bennett, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Benzel-Broll, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Bronson-Bryan, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Calhoun-Conroy, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Dall-Dworshak, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Eastman-Evans, S.C., 1995 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Farrand-Furman, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Gachot-Gazeman, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Haas-Hyman, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Kamf-Kutner, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Lacy-Lyon, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Maasen-Martin, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Mathias-Minney, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Minus-Muskat, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1a)
      - Najarian-Owen, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Paden-Putch, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Quackenbush-Rusnak, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Sacco-Shepard, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 4a)
      - Sherin-Stern, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Stern-Tyson, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Uehling-Vojir, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 6a)
      - Wahlculet-Wunsch, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Yamamoto-Zuckerbraun, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Family income
      - A-H, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - I-O, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - P-Z, 1979-1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Missing transcripts and non-applicants, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Pre-med student study
    - Premedical office statistics, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Applicant profiles and statistical data, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
  - Reports and papers, Salary equity, 1975-1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Data clean-up, Salary equity, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative action compliance-reports and memoranda, 1982-1985 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Affirmative action-Corporation report, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Sexual harassment procedures study (Yale College)-draft questionnaires and memoranda, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Profile of Institutions of Higher Education-State of Connecticut legislation drafts, notes, and memoranda, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Connecticut State Postsecondary Review Entities (SPRE) regulations-reports and memonranda, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Yale College experience and post-college planning study, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Top American research universities study, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Cooper study-minority students in Yale College, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Yale College admissions-admitted students history (Class of 1985) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Yale College admissions-admitted students history (Class of 1986) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - FAS Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty (CESOF)-includes responses from the Provost
    - 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 6-6a)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 12-13)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 14-15)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - CESOF child care study-includes correspondence, 1986-1994 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - FAS Faculty salaries-illustrative comparison
    - 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Hartigan Committee on FAS faculty appointment process-analyses and data, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - FAS faculty flow model, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Salary regression for Jaynes Committee on faculty recruitment, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - FAS faculty appointment process-Ray Novak Committee, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - FAS faculty appointments memoranda, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Yale College faculty committee-info for committee, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Union and Yale statements and articles-1984 Strike (Box 16, Folder 31-32)
  - Analyses for Ray Fair on gender and pay among union workers, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Gender and salary data of union workers, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - 1984 Strike notes-gender and salary (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - FAS salary structure, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - FAS faculty salary regressions
    - 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - FAS faculty slots, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - FAS faculty counts, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 26-27)
  - FAS faculty counts non-ladder
    - 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 30-31)
  - FAS faculty counts 2001 presentation, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - FAS faculty counts women/men appointments, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - FAS faculty counts-data for the Yale Corporation, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - FAS faculty counts-equal opportunity, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - FAS faculty counts and gender-MIT meetings, 1995-2004 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - FAS faculty counts and gender-Nancy Hopkins, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - FAS faculty counts- Lloyd Suttle, 2003-2006 (Box 17, Folder 38a-38c)
  - FAS faculty counts-Association of American Universities Data Exchange (AAUDE), 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - FAS new faculty
    - 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - FAS faculty size comparisons, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - FAS faculty counts-full time employees (FTE)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - FAS faculty demography, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - FAS faculty salaries-memoranda, reports and analyses
    - 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 11-12)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - 2001 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - 2008-2009 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Faculty salaries-Fran Holloway meeting, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Faculty salaries-long term issues, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Faculty salaries-background, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Faculty salaries by department, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Faculty salaries-working papers, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - COHFE faculty salary survey, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Faculty salary comparisons
    - 1979 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - 1981-1984 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - 1993 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Integrated Postsecondary Education Data System (IPEDS) human resources survey, 2008-2009 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - FAS faculty salary budget
    - 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - 2001 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Faculty salaries-year to year change, 1983-2014 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Faculty salary increases
    - 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Salary raise processes
    - 1990 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - 1991 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - 1992 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - 1993 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Bureau of Labor Statistics salary survey, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - COFHE correspondence (non-Yale), 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - COFHE correspondence (non-Yale), 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - COFHE environmental scanning (non-Yale), 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - COFHE surveys (non-Yale), 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - COFHE dashboard examples (non-Yale), 2004 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - COHFE institutional research (IR) seminar and survey schedule
    - 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - 1999 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - 2000 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - COHFE faculty salary report- non-Yale, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 18a)
  - COHFE organizational memoranda, lists and correspondence (non-Yale), 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - COHFE profile-FAS, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Cost of living-regional (non-Yale), 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Cost of living-state taxes (non-Yale), 1987 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Retirement surveys (non-Yale), 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Penn State retirement study, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Joseph Pettit alumni survey project (non-Yale), 1987 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Stanford University faculty reports, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - University of California pay scales, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Tufts University EDUCOM data sharing, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Northeast Association for Insitutitional Research (NEAIR) conference ephemera and membership list, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Connecticut Institutional Assessment Conference, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Fringe benefits-Columbia University, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - National Study of Post-Secondary Faculty, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Federal budget FY 1990 (non-Yale), 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 33a)
  - National price indices, 1985-1993 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Mellon Fellow evaluations-Yale College, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Retention and graduation rates-Yale College, 1981-1989 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Term bill and financial aid-Yale College, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Term bill and financial aid-Yale College, 1989-1989 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Reaccreditation-Yale College, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Student life issues: admissions and security-Yale College, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Tuition and income trends-Yale College, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - International and area studies-Yale College, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Mellon Study-Yale College, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Athletics: NCAA/Bradley-Yale College, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Student records system-field mapping (master), Undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Student record system-Yale College, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Registrar YALESTU system conversion to Banner-codes and field mappings, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Class size/teaching load-Yale College, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Class size-Yale College, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Bromley Committee, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Yale School of Management-faculty salary surveys, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Admissions: deans meetings-Yale College, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Admissions study-Yale College, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Admissions on SAT as measure-Yale College, 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Admissions-Yale College, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Admissions withdrawl study-Yale College, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Association of Universities for Research in Astronomy (AURA)-FAS correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - University Corporation for Atmospheric Research (UCAR)-faculty salaries correspondence and survey, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Bromley Committee-sponsored research, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF) Post-doctoral students survey
    - 2000 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Retirement working group, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Nordhaus retirement committee, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - COFHE faculty retirement, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Faculty retirement bibliography, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Faculty retirement report/memos-Yale and non-Yale, 1992-1998 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Faculty flow-new hires and departures, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Retirement projection model, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - YURAP completion monitoring model
    - 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - 2003 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - 2004 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - 2005 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - YURAP monitoring model, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - YURAP technical information, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - John R. Goldin report on EFPM formula and the Yale budget, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Office of the Provost-retirement reports and correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - OIR activities seminar-Southern Connecticut State University, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - OIR budget and raises, 1992-2000 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - John R. Goldin requests for information and replies
    - 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Pierre Hohenberg-faculty retirement promises, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - OIR activities
    - 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 37-37a)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 39a)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 40-40a)
    - 1988-1999 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 42-42a)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - OIR-Nordhaus correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - John R. Goldin petition, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Student race codes: Cheskis-Gold memo, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - GESO issues, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Faculty compensation and composition in the Arts and Sciences, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - FAS faculty salary survey-Columbia University
    - 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 2a)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - FAS faculty salary survey-MIT
    - 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - 2004 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Faculty salary survey-Carnegie Mellon, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP) faculty salary survey
    - 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - COHFE faculty salary survey
    - 1993 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 30-31)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - 2010 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - COHFE faculty salary survey non-Yale (Cornell), 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Faculty salaries-IPEDS, 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Faculty counts-employees by assigned position, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Faculty salary increases, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Faculty salary survey-College and University Personnel Association (CUPA), 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Faculty salary survey-Modern Language Association (MLA), 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Faculty tenure policies, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Faculty status-unpaid associates, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Faculty policies surveys, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Faculty salaries-manfile and payroll checks, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - NSF equipment survey questionnaires (Westat), 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - GRE undergraduate institution summary statistics reports, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Yale College graduation rates, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - OIR senior study-additional analyses of several years' graduates, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Career advisory and placement materials, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Inter-university salary exchange survey report, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Class of 1989: OIR Senior Study- analyses by race (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Class of 1989: OIR Senior Study-computer analyses for report tables (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Class of 1984 Senior Study (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
  - Senior Profile Study report-Class of 1980 (Box 22, Folder 4-7)